Walter Snow Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Journalistic Works, undated, 1927-1941, 1959-1973
  - Subseries B: Clippings, undated, 1927-1971
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1966-1967 (Box 3:, Folder 117)
      - "Time of Your Life Lives (Almost) Up to Title at UC", 1966 July 20
      - "Early Bernard Shaw is Delight at Uconn's Nutmeg", 1966 July 27
      - "Look Back in Anger Still Reaches for Stars at Uconn", 1966 August 2
      - "Kaufman-Hart Farce Still Prescription for Laughter", 1966 August 10
      - "Sea Tragedy of Billy Budd Unforgettable on UC Stage", 1966 October 24
      - "Uconn Player's Romp in 1908 French Farce", 1966 November 14
      - "Tigerish 'Women' Delight Uconn Theatre Audiences", 1966 December 5
      - "UC's Dr. Carlson Analyzes Poe's Belated Recognition", 1966 December 14
      - "Ugo Betti's Corrupt Judges Get Dramatic Justice at UC", 1967 January 13
      - "Scrap of Paper Is Comic 'Sardoudledom'", 1967 February 27
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1967 (Box 3:, Folder 118)
      - "UC Graduate Director Offers Vivid Becket,", 1967 March 1
      - "Wuthering Heights Both Gothic and Epic", 1967 April 3
      - "Once Upon a Mattress Is for Vaudeville Fans", 1967 April 26
      - "Taming of Shrew Is Mischievous and Gay", 1967 May 15
      - "Two Licensed Pilots Join CAP Squadron", 1967 June 20
      - "Stop the World Proves Delight at UC Nutmeg", 1967 June 28
      - "Luv Skirts Thin Ice; Proves UC Laugh-Riot", 1967 July 9
      - "Arsenic and Old Lace Still Hits Hilarious Pace", 1967 July 12
      - "Rhinoceros Is Off-Beat But Theatrically Exciting", 1967 July 19
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1967-1968 (Box 4:, Folder 119)
      - "Charley's Aunt Is Still Laugh Riot at Uconn", 1967 August 2
      - "Marat-de Sade Is Shocker And Intellectual Challenge", 1967 August 9
      - "Nutmeg Theatre Attendance Soars 24% Over Last Year", 1967 August 14
      - "Nutmeg Audiences Called Conscious of Fashion, Hits", 1967 August 15
      - Letter complimenting Snow on previous two articles from University of Connecticut, 1967 August 22
      - "Imperial Production of Camus' Caligula Is Offered at Uconn", 1967 October 23
      - "The Knack, on Uconn Stage, Proves Funnier Than Movie", 1967 November 13
      - "Lady Windermere's Fan Is Witty, Colorful (Mostly)", 1967 December 4
      - "UC's Dr. Carlson Presents Enigmatic Poe's Treasures", 1968 January 10
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1968 (Box 4:, Folder 120)
      - "Gennesaret Is Tragedy Of Crime and Revenge", 1968 March 11
      - "Brecht's Mother Courage Is Exciting Anti-War Epic", 1968, March 25
      - "Life-size Puppets, Dragon Create Colorful UC Mikado,", 1968 April 22
      - "UC Dramatist to Have New Play Offered in Storrs", 1968 April 29
      - "Carnival Atmosphere Reigns as Total Theatre Arrives", 1968 May 6
      - "Three 'Existentialist Plays,' Four Comedies Set at Uconn", 1968 May 18
      - "Albee's Tiny Alice Is Expertly-Played Riddle, June 27, 1968, 1968 June 27
      - "Hot Summer Explosion Is Averted by Parley Here", 1968 July 2
      - "State Drama Critics To Attend O'Neill Parley", 1968 July 6
      - "Pirandello's Masterpiece Is Electrifying at Nutmeg", 1968 July 10
      - "Playwrights, Critics Open O'Neill Conference Sunday, July 13, 1968, 1968 July 13
      - "O'Neill Memorial Foundation Offers Ghetto Tragedy by New Black Playwright," & "Barefoot in the Park Proves Funnier on Stage Than as Film", 1968 July 18
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1968 (Box 4:, Folder 121)
      - "The Balcony Due at Uconn; Genet's Satirical Fantasy", 1968 July 20
      - "O'Neill Foundation Offers 1-Act Comedy and Drama", 1968 July 22
      - "Sail Along Sound Inspires Idea Of O'Neill Memorial", 1968 July 23
      - "Nutmeg's Balcony is Daring, Spectacular", 1968 July 24
      - "2 O'Neil Playwrights Try New Techniques", 1968 July 29
      - "Fjelde Translates Ibsen, Attends O'Neill Parley", 1968 July 30
      - "Male Animal Is Campus Treat and Laugh-Riot", 1968 July 31
      - "Androcles and Lion to Close Nutmeg Season Next Week'", 1968 August 2
      - "'Private Ear,' 'Public Eye' Are Funny, Human, Wise", 1968 August 4
      - "Summertree Playwright Scores Again", 1968 August 5
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1968 (Box 4:, Folder 122)
      - "Androcles Combines Farce, Comedy, Pageant", 1968 August 7
      - "Hilarious Show Has UC Box office Troubles", 1968 August 12
      - "Should It Aviod Drama, Stick to Comedy", 1968 August 14
      - "Do You Want to Read a Good Story? 60 Best Novels Are Selected", 1968 September 5
      - "London Bobbies Keep Queen's Peace' Without Guns", 1968 October 9
      - "London Streets, Ancient Names, Invoke Magic; 'Still Fairest City in World'", 1968 October 10
      - "London Offers 35 Plays to Broadway's 15", 1968 October 15
      - "High Broadway Costs Will Bar Importation of Some London Hits", 1968 October 16
      - "Luftwaffe Blasted Third of Canterbury, Barely Missed Gothic Cathedral", 1968 October 23
      - "Nightingales Leave Hampstead, Keats' Music Lingers", 1968 October 28
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1968-1969 (Box 4:, Folder 123)
      - "Homecoming Gets Mixed Reaction", 1968 October 28
      - "Dr. Johnson's 'Dictionary House' Is Restored After Three Bombings", 1968 November 11
      - "Othello Is Cool Hepcat in Uneven Uconn Revival", 1968 November 18
      - "Haunted and Haunting Poe Offered in UC Monologue", 1968 December 5
      - "House of Bernard Alba Offered at UC Theatre", 1968 December 10
      - "Confrontation '69 Jibes Gently at Rebels, Brass", 1969 February 22
      - "Caldwell Remains Giant; Stories Stand Test of Time", 1969 March 1
      - "Rice's Adding Machine Proves Exciting, Timely", 1969 March 17
      - "Vet's Homecoming Is Haunting UC Drama", 1969 March 26
      - "Jack Conroy, Bontemps to Talk at Uconn", 1969 April 4
      - "Senior Follies Scores; Shafer Audience Roars", 1969 April 12
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1969 (Box 4:, Folder 124)
      - "Summertree at Uconn Is Beautiful and Haunting", 1969 April 14
      - "Forgotten Novel Hailed as Classic, Jack Conroy is at Uconn for 2.5 Days", 1969 April 15
      - "5 Northward Migrations Is Topic at Uconn's Friday", 1969 April 16
      - "UC's Imaginative Directions Enhances 3 One-Acters", 1969 April 21
      - "Quality Paperbacks Designed for Students", 1969 April 22
      - "Mary Lavin's Irish Romance is Revealed", 1969 April 23
      - "New York is Fabulous City in Springtime as Sea Breeze Banishes Smog", 1969 April 29
      - "McWilliams, Cowley Speak at UC Tribute", 1969 April 30
      - "Threepenny Opera Scores As Uconn Theatre Finale", 1969 May 2
      - "Grapes of Wrath Hailed By Cowley as 'U.S. Epic'", 1969 May 3
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1969 (Box 4:, Folder 125)
      - "B. Tavern's Cotton-Pickers Is Autobiographical Novel", 1969 May 14
      - "If It's Tuesday, This Must Be Belgium!, Why Not 3 Full Weeks in Britain?", 1969 May 27
      - "Prices Lower In England But Trip Isn't Cheap", 1969 May 28
      - "Odd Couple Still Proves Laugh-Riot at Uconn's Nutmeg Playhouse", 1969 June 25
      - "Uconn's 'Semester of Thirties' Highlighted B. Traven, Neglected Novelist", 1969 June 30
      - "Brian Friel's Lovers Is Darlin' Evening at UC", 1969 July 2
      - "Nutmeg Players Brilliantly Recreate 12th Century Palace Crisis", 1969 July 10
      - "Eugene O'Neill Troupe Offering 17 New Plays in Month", 1969 July 14
      - "Nutmeg Clowns Are Riots in Funniest of French Farces at Uconn", 1969 July 16
      - "Director of Marat-Sade Will Stage Loot at Uconn", 1969 July 19
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1969 (Box 4:, Folder 126)
      - "Uproarious Comedy at Wake? Loot Offers Macabre Mirth at UC Nutmeg", 1969 July 22
      - "Summer's Biggest Audience Hails Albee's Sardonic Comedy at Nutmeg", 1969 July 30
      - "Mansfield's Wormwood Review is Moving to California After 9 Years", 1969 August 4
      - "Jean Brodie Is in Her Prime; Wins Nutmeg Applause, Cheers", 1969 August 6
      - "Woman Skyjacker Used Name of Dead Guerrilla", 1969 September 2
      - "Chronicle Writer Finds Abbotsford Is Monument to Dreams, Folly", 1969 October 18
      - "Royal Hunt of the Sun Is Colorful But Uneven Uconn Spectacle", 1969 October 27
      - "Chronicle Writer Rediscovers Scott and Tours 'Lady of Lake' Country", 1969 November 10
      - "Rimers of Eldritch Proves Grim Drama of Ghost Town", 1969 November 17
      - "Ruines of Border Abbeys Intrigued Walter Scott and Still Haunt Tourists", 1969 December 1
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1969-1970 (Box 4:, Folder 127)
      - "Edinburgh Tour Reveals Old Scandals, Scenic Delights", 1969 December 8
      - "UC Offers Haunting Version of O'Neill's Long Day's Journey Into Night, December 9, 1969
      - "New Scotland Yard's 'Black Museum' Recalls Grim Murders, Clever Spies", 1969 December 15
      - "Police Doctors Can Blunder, Touring Writer Learns", 1969 December 16
      - "Chronicle Writer, Visiting Stratford-Upon-Avon, Finds Magic Tops Over-Commercialization", 1970 January 15
      - "Chronicle Writer Tours Estates of Shakespeare, Landowner and Poet", 1970 January 16
      - "Chronicle Writer Visits Great Garden, Recalls Poet's Love of Flowers", 1970 January 20
      - "Queen and Rebels' Offered at Arena Theatre", 1970 February 23
      - "Lysistata, 2,400 Years Old, Proves Rowdy, Timely Antiwar Satire at UC", 1970 March 9
      - "Wormwood Review, Long Published in Storrs, Thrives in California", 1970 March 18
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1970 (Box 4:, Folder 128)
      - "Poet Wordsworth's Bi-Centenary Opens", 1970 April 3
      - "How Doctor and Barber Became Associated in Fantasticks Show", 1970 April 4
      - "Dickens's London Is Spotlighted on 100th Anniversary", 1970 April 6
      - "Dickens's House Is Preserved in London", 1970 April 7
      - "Trouble With Lawyers Bares Banditry at Bar", 1970 April 9
      - "Roar of Greasepaint Is Tuneful, Lively But--", 1970 April 13
      - "Love for Three Oranges Best of UC Puppet Shows", 1970 May 4
      - "Star-Spangled Girl Sparkles at Uconn", 1970 June 24
      - "'Blackout Comedy' Should be Title of UC's Hilarious Farce", 1970 July 1
      - "Noel Coward's Comedies Of Twenties Score Again", 1970 July 6
      - "Hay Fever Is Still Madcap Frolic at UC", 1970 July 8
      - "Title Role of Bernard Shaw's Candida Goal of Actresses Now; Once Was Shunned", 1970 July 11
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1970 (Box 4:, Folder 129)
      - "Shaw's Candida Is Still Delightful and Timely at Uconn's Nutmeg", 1970 July 15
      - "Feiffer's Little Murders Is Hilarious Nightmare", 1970 July 22
      - "Dietz Proves Fabulous Clown in Moliere's Miser at UC", 1970 July 29
      - "Bernard Shaw's Devil's Disciple in Top Form", 1970 August 3
      - "Romantic Ghosts of Past Haunt Camino Real at UC", 1970 August 5
      - "All's Well Evokes Curious Modern Moods With Story of Lady Doctor and Rebellious Youth", 1970 August 24
      - "Shakespeare Theatre Seeks Votes on Next Year's 3 Plays", 1970 August 25
      - "Coventry House Shook; Trees Bent Double As Baby Tornado Hit", 1970 August 31
      - "It Can Carry More Than Horses and Surreys Now: Gurleyville Bridge Joins Modern Era", 1970 September 8
      - "Does Wall Street Face New Bearish Trend or Will the Bulls Return?", 1970 November 16
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1970-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 130)
      - "Pinter's Birthday Party Mixes Laughs, Terror at UC", 1970 November 16
      - "Roller-Coaster Story of Writer's Life", 1970 November 28
      - "Dracula Hailed at UC as Scary 'Camp'", 1970 December 7
      - "That's right, we interviewed Mr. Groundhog", 1971 February 2
      - "British drama at Uconn seems My Lai aftermath", 1971 February 15
      - "Bookseller-poet Briggs starred posthumously in 'little mag'", 1971 February 24
      - "Saved, British shocker, at UC", 1971 March 1
      - "Voice that is great within us' is great but flawed anthology", 1971 March 6
      - "Hogan's Goat, at UC playhouse, is poetic tragedy of Irish politics", 1971 March 22
      - "Eastern's poet-professor maps two projects in Denmark", 1971 April 24
    - Willimantic Chronicle (Box 4:, Folder 131)
      - "Poetic renaissance in area? 12 bards are getting in print", 1971 May 8
      - "Luck favors Chronicle reporter; misses Mediterranean disasters, strikes", 1971 June 30
      - "Man of La Mancha again wins ovation at UC's Nutmeg summer theatre", 1971 June 30
      - "Chronicle report on 23rd hour plan to aid periled wonder-city of Venice", 1971 July 3
      - "Chronicle reporter visits 16 Mediterranean ports of old Roman Empire", 1971 July 7
      - "Owl, Pussycat wins laughs…laughter at UC's Nutmeg", 1971 July 7
      - "Old Dubrovnik is best preserved fortified medieval port", 1971 July 14
      - "Cactus Flower is Nutmeg frolic", 1971 July 14
      - "'Pleasure Dome' of Diocletian", 1971 July 21
      - "Last Sweet Days of Isaac surprise and delight at UC", 1971 July 21
    - Willimantic Chronicle, 1971 (Box 4:, Folder 132)
      - "Imagination need to visualize ancient Olympia", 1971 July 28
      - "Ruined Parthenon's glory", 1971 August 4
      - "Adaptation and Next are Nutmeg double bill", 1971 August 4
      - "What happened to Troy's treasure in World War II?", 1971 August 11
      - "Lovely War scores at Uconn", 1971 August 11
      - "Istanbul skyline: 1,000 minarets", 1971 August 18
      - "Mosques of Turkish conquerors contrasted with Topkapi harem scandals", 1971 August 25
      - "Ephesus ruins evoke city", 1971 September 1
      - "Carlson shows Poe's tale still provokes controversy", 1971 October 16
      - "Coventry Bookstore auctions inventory today", 1971 October 16
    - Letters to the Editor, 1971-1973 (Box 4:, Folder 133)
      - "Rockefeller"
      - "Israeli Bombings"
      - "Steele on the spot"
      - "No 'Hairy' Ape"
      - "Untitled"
      - "Horrified"
      - "The big lie"
      - "Praise for Page 8"
      - "Boiler room tactics"
    - Willimantic Chronicle, undated (Box 4:, Folder 134)
      - "Vintage Cops of Air Magazine"
- Series IV: Fictional Works, undated, 1928-1973
  - Subseries A: Novels, undated, 1933-1969
    - "Bank Run in Harlem's 'Little Italy'" excerpt from novel The Magnificent Marchetti, published in International Literature, 1933 (Box 4:, Folder 135)
    - "Lunch Hour in Wall Street" excerpt from novel The Magnificent Marchetti published in The Anvil (Jack Conroy), 1933 (Box 4:, Folder 136)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti early draft with corrections, pages 1-113, 1933 (Box 4:, Folder 137)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti early draft with corrections, pages 114 -237A, 1933 (Box 4:, Folder 138)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti early draft with corrections, pages 237B-250C, 1933 (Box 4:, Folder 139)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti early draft with corrections, pages 251-367A, 1933 (Box 5:, Folder 140)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti, early draft with corrections, pages pages 368-468, 1933 (Box 5:, Folder 141)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti manuscript, pages 1-133, 1933 (Box 5:, Folder 142)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti manuscript, pages 134-240, 1933 (Box 5:, Folder 143)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti manuscript, pages 241-330, 1933 (Box 5:, Folder 144)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti manuscript, pages 331-440, 1933 (Box 5:, Folder 145)
    - The Magnificent Marchetti manuscript, pages 441-603, 1933 (Box 5:, Folder 146)
    - Notes on Southern New England Textile Mills for Against Destiny (early version of Silent Weave the Mills), circa 1934 (Box 5:, Folder 147)
    - Against Destiny (early version of Silent Weave the Mills), circa 1934 (Box 5:, Folder 148)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys manuscript with corrections, pages 1-82, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 149)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys manuscript with corrections, pages 83-163, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 150)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys manuscript with corrections, pages 164-279, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 151)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys carbon copy sent to publisher, pages 1-61, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 152)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys carbon copy sent to publisher, pages 62-105, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 153)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys carbon copy sent to publisher, pages 106-138, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 154)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys carbon copy sent to publisher, pages 139-177, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 155)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys carbon copy sent to publisher, pages 178-235, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 156)
    - Silent Weave the Mills: A Novel of New England's Textile Valleys carbon copy sent to publisher, pages 237-279, circa 1941 (Box 6:, Folder 157)
    - The Dazzled and the Damned outline and several revisions of three chapters, 1951 (Box 6:, Folder 158)
    - The Dazzled and the Damned third version with annotations, pages 1-27, 1951 (Box 6:, Folder 159)
    - The Dazzled and the Damned third version with annotations, pages 28-86, 1951 (Box 6:, Folder 160)
    - The Dazzled and the Damned third version with annotations, pages 87-144, 1951 (Box 6:, Folder 161)
    - The Gaugin Murders fourth version of revised typescript with annotations, pages 1-73, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 162)
    - The Gaugin Murders fourth version of revised typescript with annotations, pages 74-131, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 163)
    - The Gaugin Murders fourth version of revised typescript with annotations, pages 132-198, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 164)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 407-441, undated (Box 7:, Folder 165)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 442-490, undated (Box 7:, Folder 166)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 491-535, undated (Box 7:, Folder 167)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 536-560, undated (Box 7:, Folder 168)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 561-588, undated (Box 7:, Folder 169)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 590-615, undated (Box 7:, Folder 170)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 616-651, undated (Box 7:, Folder 171)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 652-686, undated (Box 7:, Folder 172)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 687-716, undated (Box 7:, Folder 173)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 717-742, undated (Box 7:, Folder 174)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 743-763, undated (Box 7:, Folder 175)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 766-781, undated (Box 7:, Folder 176)
    - The Private Life of George Gissing manuscript, pages 782-794, undated (Box 7:, Folder 177)
    - The Liberators: a Novel of the Negro-Abolitionist Struggles for Freedom in the Civil War incomplete manuscript, pages 1-33, undated (Box 7:, Folder 178)
    - The Liberators: a Novel of the Negro-Abolitionist Struggles for Freedom in the Civil War incomplete manuscript, pages 34-65, undated (Box 7:, Folder 179)
    - The Liberators: a Novel of the Negro-Abolitionist Struggles for Freedom in the Civil War incomplete manuscript, pages 66-105, undated (Box 7:, Folder 180)
    - The Liberators: a Novel of the Negro-Abolitionist Struggles for Freedom in the Civil War incomplete manuscript, pages 106-145, undated (Box 7:, Folder 181)
    - The Liberators: a Novel of the Negro-Abolitionist Struggles for Freedom in the Civil War incomplete manuscript, pages 146-174, undated (Box 7:, Folder 182)
    - The Liberators: a Novel of the Negro-Abolitionist Struggles for Freedom in the Civil War outline, undated (Box 7:, Folder 183)
  - Subseries B: Plays, 1941, 1968
    - "Our Way of Life" one-act parody, 1941 (Box 7:, Folder 184)
    - "Law and Order Forever" one-act play, 1968 (Box 7:, Folder 184)
  - Subseries C: Poetry, undated, 1927-1972
    - Early Poems, undated (Box 8:, Folder 186)
      - "Goliath", 1930
      - "Social Worker", published in the Rebel Poet, 1931
      - "The New Statistics", 1931
      - "Rejections", 1941
      - "General W. T. Sherman: The Destroyer", circa 1942
      - "Priapus", 1944
      - "Faneuil Hall, Boston", undated
      - "12:20 A.M. August 23, 1927", published in The Daily Worker, 1927 August 27
      - "Columbine, Colorado", published in The Daily Worker, 1927 November 26
    - Nine Poems, circa 1931 (Box 8:, Folder 187)
      - "Goliath"
      - "The Duped"
      - "Sons of Earth"
      - "The Revolutionary Poet"
      - "A Textile Worker's Prayer"
      - "Flophouse Nocturne"
      - "To Shelley"
      - "The South Sea Romanticist"
      - "To Jack Conroy, On His Story, 'Pipe Line.'"
    - Unrest, ed. Jack Conroy and Ralph Cheney, "A Striker Speaks", 1931 (Box 8:, Folder 188)
    - "A Dirge for England", 1937 (Box 8:, Folder 189)
    - "Sonnets to Theodosia", 1940 (Box 8:, Folder 190)
      - "Encounter"
      - "Reflection"
      - "The Modern Venus"
      - "Doubting Thomas"
      - "The Lost Sonnet"
      - "Of Patience"
      - "Earthy Poetry"
    - "Five Portraits of Liberators" published in The Negro Quarterly, 1942
      - "John Brown: The Avenger"
      - "Frederick Douglas: Voice of His People"
      - "Thaddeus Stevens: The Slandered"
      - "Robert B. Elliott: Tribune in Congress"
      - "Senator Charles Sumner: Enlightened Hatred"
    - Sonnets published in Wormwood Review, 1970 (Box 8:, Folder 191)
      - "New York"
      - "The Muse of Youth"
      - "The Villa in Hampstead"
    - Drafts and revisions of "Bound in Shallows (Ben Johnson Recalls an Obscure Play Right)", 1970-1971 (Box 8:, Folder 192)
    - "Bound in Shallows (Ben Johnson Recalls an Obscure Play Right)" with annotations and correspondence from Marvin Malone, 1970-1971 (Box 8:, Folder 193)
    - Correspondence of reaction to "Bound in Shallows (Ben Johnson Recalls an Obscure Play Right),", undated (Box 8:, Folder 194)
    - Published version of "Robert Browning at Sunset and Midday" in Wormwood Review with drafts and revisions, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 195)
    - Correspondence of reaction to "Robert Browning at Sunset and Midday", circa 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 196)
    - Program for solo poetry reading with accompanying commentary and correspondence, 1971 January 31 (Box 8:, Folder 197)
      - "The 'Nigger' He Killed"
      - "September 13, 1971"
    - Program for solo poetry reading with accompanying commentary and correspondence, 1971 October 17 (Box 8:, Folder 198)
    - The Glory and the Shame, drafts and notes on title poem, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 199)
    - The Glory and the Shame, drafts and notes on title poem, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 200)
    - The Glory and the Shame, drafts and notes on title poem, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 201)
    - The Glory and the Shame, drafts and notes on title poem, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 202)
    - The Glory and the Shame, drafts and notes on title poem, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 203)
    - The Glory and the Shame, drafts and notes on title poem, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 204)
    - The Glory and the Shame, carbon copies of poems with annotations and notes, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 205)
    - The Glory and the Shame, carbon copies of poems with annotations and notes, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 206)
    - The Glory and the Shame, carbon copies of poems with annotations and notes, 1971-1972 (Box 9:, Folder 207)
    - The Glory and the Shame, carbon copies of poems with annotations and notes, 1971-1972 (Box 9:, Folder 208)
    - The Glory and the Shame, photocopy, 1971-1972 (Box 9:, Folder 209)
    - The Glory and the Shame, corrected copies, 1971-1972 (Box 9:, Folder 210)